A Guide to the Green Hills Garden Club yearbooks, 1954-1993
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Green Hills Garden Club yearbooks, 1954-1993
The Library of Virginia
51336
.45 cubic feet and 1 box
Green Hills Garden Club
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Green Hills Garden Club of Raphine, JoAnn Pendley, president.
Historical Information
The Green Hills Garden Club is located in Raphine, Rockbridge County, Virginia. The club was organized 29 June 1948.
Scope and Content
Yearbooks, 1954-1986, of the Green Hills Garden Club of Raphine, Rockbridge County, Virginia, providing membership lists and information on upcoming programs. Collection also contains the yearbook for the College Park Garden Club (1965-1966), the Park View Garden Club (1966-1967), and the Country Gardeners (1966-1967), all of Staunton, Virginia. Also contains a district devotions book, 1989, for the Shenandoah District of the Virginia Federation of Garden Clubs, and a poem about gardens copied in 1993.
Contents List
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1954-1955 (Folder 1)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1955-1956 (Folder 2)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1961-1962 (Folder 3)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1962-1963 (Folder 4)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1963-1964 (Folder 5)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1964-1965 (Folder 6)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies, 1 with handwritten section), 1965-1966 (Folder 7)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1966-1967 (Folder 8)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies, handwritten alterations to 1966-1967 yearbook), 1967-1968 (Folder 9)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies, 1 with handwritten changes), 1967-1968 (Folder 10)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1968-1969 (Folder 11)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1969-1970 (Folder 12)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1970-1971 (Folder 13)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1971-1972 (Folder 14)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1972-1973 (Folder 15)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1973-1974 (Folder 16)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1974-1975) (Folder 17)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1975-1976 (Folder 18)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1976-1977 (Folder 19)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1978-1979 (Folder 20)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1979-1980 (Folder 21)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1981-1982 (Folder 22)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (3 copies, handwritten changes in 2), 1982-1983 (Folder 23)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1983-1984 (Folder 24)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook (2 copies), 1984-1985 (Folder 25)
- Green Hills Garden Club yearbook, 1985-1986 (Folder 26)
- College Park Garden Club (Staunton, Va.) yearbook, 1965-1966 (Folder 27)
- Country Gardeners (Staunton, Va.) yearbook, 1966-1967 (Folder 28)
- Park View Garden Club (Staunton, Va.) yearbook, 1966-1967 (Folder 29)
- Virginia Federation of Garden Clubs, Shenandoah District devotions, 1989 (Folder 30)
- Poem--garden collect for yearbook, 1993 (Folder 31)